Sandeep Renjith Sr Escalation Engineer - Infoblox

Current Profile

Part of support tiger teams for handling customer issues for certain critical accounts on specific products and features. Providing training, guidance and mentoring for Tier-1 and Tier-2 engineers. Creating training content and learning paths for Infoblox products and features. Creating KB articles. Reviewing and publishing KB articles created by Tier-1 and Tier-2 engineers.

Functioning as Support SME on DNS, DNS Security, API, PKI, SNMP and Infoblox integration with AWS, Azure, Openstack and VMware VRealize. Infoblox SaaS solutions and Infoblox Subscriber Services.

Active member of Infoblox Experts Community.

Key role in creation of several automation solution for Infoblox Support such as tools for log analysis, a lab automation system for automated deployment and termination of Infoblox VMs on vCenter etc.

Relevant Projects

MDCMS (Markdown Content Management System)

MDCMS is a content management system with which a simple blogging website can be deployed within minutes.

MDCMS is written in Go.

Links:

Project: https://github.com/sandeeprenjith/mdcms

Docker: https://hub.docker.com/r/rensande/mdcms/

Example site built with MDCMS: http://www.bytesarena.com

Personal Info

Address

Vipanjika, ASRA 49, Attinkuzhy, Trivandrum

Phone

+91 9496493507 +91 8157057314

E-mail

sandeep.renjith@gmail.com srenjith@infoblox.com

Date of birth

1991-09-16

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sandeep-renjith-72969859

Website

http://www.bytesarena.com

Precompiled binaries (Windows, Linux, Mac): http://www.bytesarena.com/downloads/

Skills

DNSSEC and Infoblox

Most recent article in Infoblox Community.

https://community.infoblox.com/t5/Best-Practices/DNSSEC-and-Infoblox/ba-p/13076

DNS Anycast Lab

DNS Anycast learning environment with Docker

https://bitbucket.org/rensande/dns-anycast-lab

NIOS ((Infoblox)) Proficient

DNS Proficient

DHCP Proficient

Python Above intermediate

Docker Above intermediate

Kubernetes Above Intermediate

Azure Above Intermediate

Linux Above intermediate

BASH Above Intermediate

SNMP Above Intermediate

Openstack Intermediate

Go Intermediate

AWS Intermediate

Perl Intermediate

HTML Intermediate

CSS Intermediate

Experience

2015-01-2017-01

Technical Support Engineer

ASM Technologies Ltd

Worked at Infoblox as a contractor from ASM Technologies Ltd in the role of Technical Support Engineer.

Roles and Responsibilities

Assisting customers of Infoblox with

	technical issues and configuration relating to Infoblox Products as well as protocol services such as DNS, DHCP, NTP, SNMP etc. via phone and email. Assisting customers with Infoblox integration with products from various vendors. Creating internal as well as customer facing KB articles.	
2012-10 - 2014-12	Sr Consultant, Technical Support	
	Sutherland Global Services	
	Worked at Sutherland Global Services as a Tier-2 Technical Support Consultant for the client McAfee.	
	Roles and Responsibilities	
	 Assisting customers of McAfee home antivirus products with technical issues over phone, chat and email. Handling technical escalations. Providing training and guidance to Tier-1 Technical Support consultants regarding McAfee products and Operating Systems. 	
Education		
2009-05 - 2012-04	Baselius College / Mahatma Gandhi University	
	Bachelor of Commerce - 2012	